Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2019-0084, 2001; 2015-2019
  - Athletic Training: Summer McKeehan (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Austin Verissimo (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Ben Hummel (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: James "Jimmy" Doll (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Ryan Thompson (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Brody Huitema (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: CC Uche (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Robert Moewes (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Erik Hanson (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Joe Ohaus (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Brian White (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Noah Snyder (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Cameron Moseley (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Carter Manley (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Markus Fjørtoft (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Henry Booth (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Kevon Black (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Bryson Asher (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Jeremy Ebobisse (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Tommy Wang (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Jared Golestani (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer: Macario Hing-Glover (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Media Guide, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Statistics, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Game Notes, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Game Programs, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Clippings, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Files: Media Guide, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Files: Statistics, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Files: Game Notes, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Files: Game Programs, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Files: Clippings, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Media Guide, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Statistics, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Game Notes, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Game Programs, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Soccer Files: Clippings, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Michael Wright (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Roman Romero (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Xaviel Ramos (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Tyler Patrick (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Spencer Neff (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Garrett Neff (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Michael Monica (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Owen Lawrie (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Bailey Jack (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Michael Johnson (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Jake Faust (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Logan Day (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Joshua Copeland (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Thomas Colten (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Cole Baumgartner (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Connor Bass (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Thayer Atkins (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Wrestling: Joey Abbate (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Photos: Duke vs. St. Andrews, 2001 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Photos: Duke vs. Brown, 2001 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Photos: Duke vs. Yale, 2001 (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Women's Basketball Game by Game, February 21-March 6, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Rayah Craig (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Sofia Roma (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Faith Suggs (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Madison Treece (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Box Scores, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Media Guide, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Game Programs, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Clippings, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Caroline Andretta (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Morgan Bitting (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Tessa Gote (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Christy Palazzese (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Kiki Rozemiejer (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Erin Scherrer (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Lydia Smeltz (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Field Hockey: Rose Tynan (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Game Programs, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Play-by-Plays, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Box Scores, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Game Tracker, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Game Programs, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Play-by-Plays, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Box Scores, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Game Tracker, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Kelli Kalinoski (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Jessi Bartholomew (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Leah Meyer (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Haley Seyfarth (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Andie Shelton (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Volleyball: Tara Hittle (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Football photos (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - 2019 Fencing (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Bryn Hammarberg (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Alan Ko (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Kristen Coury (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Camille Esnault (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Rhiannon Harvey (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Bridget Wallace (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Vivian Wang (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Claudia Wrampelmeier (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Slava Zingerman (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Phoebe Caplin (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Cathy Chi (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Caitie Buteau (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Jake Shulman (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Eric Pei (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Joseph Lam (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Fencing: Will Feldman (Box UA2019-0084.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores, November 11, 2018-February 14, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.8)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Notes (Box UA2019-0084.8)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Programs (Box UA2019-0084.8)
  - Women's Basketball: Play-By-Play (Box UA2019-0084.8)
  - Swimming & Diving: Lindsey Trematerra (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: MaryEllen Targonski (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Maria Sheridan (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Anna Quinn (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Isabella Paez (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Brynne O'Shea (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Catie Miller (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Susan Hynes (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Leah Goldman (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Lizzie Devitt (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Verity Abel (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Alyssa Arwood (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Lexy Aitchison (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Mickayla Hinkle (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Maddie Hess (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Swimming & Diving: Mackenzie Willborn (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf: Celine Boutier (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf: Leona Maguire (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf: Lisa Maguire (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf: Virginia Elena Carta (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf: Eria Shepherd (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf: Megan Furtney (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Season Stats, 2016 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Team Results, 2016 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Team Roster, 2016 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Clippings, 2016 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: LSU Tiger Golf Classic Program, 2016 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Season Stats, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Team Results, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Team Roster, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Clippings, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Season Stats, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Team Results, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Team Roster, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Clippings, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: NCAA Tournament Match Notes, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf Files: Clippings, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Basketball: Play-by-Plays, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Basketball: Shot Chart, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf: Results, 2017-2018 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Golf: Results, 2018-2019 (Box UA2019-0084.9)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Notes, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Programs, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Play-by-Plays, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Erin Mathias (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Rebecca Greenwell (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Lexie Brown (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Lynee Belton (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Jaida Patrick (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Jada Claude (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Miela Goodchild (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Jennifer Ezeh (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Women's Basketball: Maria Faz Davalos (Box UA2019-0084.10)
  - Baseball: Game Programs, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Clippings, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming and Diving: Letterwinner List, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming and Diving: Roster, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming and Diving: Annual Report, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming and Diving: Season Times, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming and Diving: Program Records, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming and Diving: Media Guide, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming and Diving: Meet Results, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming and Diving: Clippings, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Ben Gross (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Adam Laskey (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Graeme Stinson (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Kennie Taylor (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Hunter Davis (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Al Pesto (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Aaron Therien (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Baseball: Kyle Gallagher (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Jason Lapidus (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Ryan Dickerson (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Vincent Lin (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Catalin Mateas (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Robert Levine (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Wrestling Files, 2018-2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Clippings, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Media Guide (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Ryan Dickerson final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Jason Lapidus final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Vincent Lin final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Tennis: Catalin Mateas final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Tennis: Kaitlyn McCarthy, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Tennis: Ellyse Hamlin (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Clippings, 2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Media Guide, 2018-2019 (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Tara Christensen final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Taji Philips final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Rhea Bergman final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Margot Calmar final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Marissa Donadio final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Hannah Ferry final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Anna Jenkins final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Isabel Ruby-Hill final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Sophie Simister final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Rowing: Shannon Tierney final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Track & Field: Charles Cooper final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Track & Field: Lyin Battle final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Track & Field: Stephen Garrett final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Track & Field: Nikhil Pulimood final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Track & Field: Rivers Rideout final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Nick Bigot (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Roger Kriegl (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Matt Johnson (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Judd Howard (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Riley Hickman (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Yusuke Legard (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Evan Moretti (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Chris Murphy (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Josh Owsiany (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Alex Pena (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Noah Stevens (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Max St. George (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Sean Tate (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Men's Swimming & Diving: Teddy Zeng (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: Olivia Gwynn final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: Kim Hallowes final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: MacKenzie Kerr final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: Liz Lansing final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: Jaida Lemmons final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: India Lowe final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: Domonique Panton final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: Nati Sheppard final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Women's Track & Field: Stefani Vukajlovic final bio (Box UA2019-0084.11)
  - Swimming & Diving: Melanie Klaren, Assistant Coach (Box UA2019-0084.11)